-是的  你不行  -的确  你逊毙了
- No, you do not. - No, you're horrible at it.
不过还有那么几次
Well, I mean, a couple times,
我送了你很好的礼物
I got you something nice.
-还记得我送你的换机油吗  -记得
- Remember I got the oil change? - Right.
-给车使的  -记得  是的
- For the car? - Right, yeah.
-特意送你的  -是啊  真"贴心"
- That was for you. - You did that, that was nice.
-是的  -今年
- Yeah. - This year,
你不必再担心啦
you don't have to worry,
因为我都准备好了
'cause I got it all figured out.
你看
Ta-da!
这是什么
What is it?
为庆祝耶稣降生的一种倒数计时月历从12月1日起  每天在对应日期打开一扇门  之后往往有惊喜情人节版耶稣降临日历
It's a Valentine's Advent calendar.
今年我们要过情人周
This year we're doing Valentine's Days.
情人周
Valentine's Days?
不必再为要把
Say good-bye to the pressure
所有的浪漫压缩到一天而压力山大啦
of being super-romantic on one day,
今年我们要在情人节前
and say hello to being somewhat-romantic
把浪漫匀给很多天
for a bunch of days leading up to the big V.
-太好了  -每扇小门背后
- Yeah! - Behind each little door is a romantic activity